<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NewsAI</title>
    <link>https://www.newsai.co/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on NewsAI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2016 14:19:00 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.newsai.co/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Sick of Updating? 4 Ways We’re Trying to Take The Pain Away From It</title>
      <link>https://www.newsai.co/blog/sick-of-updating/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2016 14:19:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.newsai.co/blog/sick-of-updating/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Not all companies have a central repository and in the cutthroat world of high powered PR, sharing information might can be a tricky task. Often times lists are stored in Excel sheets or emails and contact information is updated on an individual basis. This process is cumbersome and we want the PR professionals to know that we’re actively developing the solution. These are why we believe an update function is highly important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-less-time-editing:78492dc7016a6f7fab57acd149adea8b&#34;&gt;1. Less Time Editing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps you’ve built a list but it now needs updating — you wouldn’t want to have to go through countless sheets and documents to make this change. To alleviate this issue we sync your data with the social profiles of influencers so you don’t have to go through various sheets and documents to make a change. Less back and forth means more time seeing how your client is trending.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;2-it-streamlines-workflow:78492dc7016a6f7fab57acd149adea8b&#34;&gt;2. It Streamlines Workflow&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With information up-to-date in your rolodex, it means you can go into your project with set names in mind for who you would like to reach out to. No more thinking too long about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;3-stay-competitive:78492dc7016a6f7fab57acd149adea8b&#34;&gt;3. Stay Competitive&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As in, you get to update it without others seeing it. We get it — your list is a private one and very important to your profession. Given these parameters, we want you to have an optimal experience that doesn’t compromise your competitive edge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;4-you-can-organize-on-the-fly:78492dc7016a6f7fab57acd149adea8b&#34;&gt;4. You Can Organize On The Fly&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we said earlier, it’s all about efficiency. We also want to help you centralize the location of your media lists so you organize on the fly. We want you to have all of your highly-valued press contact information on a singular platform so you can easily search it in one place.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>